{
    "C1L1questions": [
        {
            "questionText": "What is the purpose of $LZT?",
            "option1": "Utility",
            "option2": "Gambling",
            "option3": "Meme coin",
            "option4": "A store of value",
            "answer": "A store of value"
        },
        {
            "questionText": "What is the purpose of $LAZA?",
            "option1": "A store of value",
            "option3": "Utility",
            "option2": "Meme coin",
            "option4": "Gambling",
            "answer": "Utility"
        },
        {
            "questionText": "What is the planned total circulation of $LZT?",
            "option1": "1000",
            "option2": "100 Million",
            "option3": "Every holder is issued 1 token",
            "option4": "Every holder is issued with 5 tokens",
            "answer": "100 Million"
            
        },
        {
            "questionText": "What is the native (base) currency of the XRPL?",
            "option1": "$XRP",
            "option2": "$LZT",
            "option3": "$LAZA",
            "option4": "$XRPL",
            "answer": "$XRP"
        },
        {
            "questionText": "Which of these blockchains are the cheapest/fastest?",
            "option1": "BNC",
            "option2": "ETH",
            "option3": "BTC",
            "option4": "XRPL",
            "answer": "XRPL"
        },
        {
            "questionText": "Why did Lazatech choose to make the XRPL itâ€™s home",
            "option1": "Because Jed McCaleb called us up and was very insistent",
            "option2": "Because of the high costs of transactions, speed, and efficiency",
            "option3": "Because of the low costs of transactions, speed, and efficiency",
            "option4": "Because other blockchains aren't accepting any new project launches",
            "answer": "Because of the low costs of transactions, speed, and efficiency"
            
        },
        {
            "questionText": "What does LAZA means?",
            "option1": "Help",
            "option2": "Cryptocurrency",
            "option3": "Money",
            "option4": "God has helped",
            "answer": "God has helped"
        },
        {
            "questionText": "Does Lazatech Soc Med gives token to its users?",
            "option1": "Yes",
            "option2": "No",
            "option3": "Sometimes",
            "option4": "Yes but you need to pay",
            "answer": "Yes"
        },
        {
            "questionText": "Does Lazatech Educate give you knowledge of the social media counterpart of it?",
            "option1": "Not at all",
            "option2": "A little",
            "option3": "Yes but not enough",
            "option4": "Yes",
            "answer": "Yes"
        },
        {
            "questionText": "Does Lazatech Educate ensure that its its are knowledgeable before entering its social media counterpart and the XRPL ledger blockchain?",
            "option1": "Yes",
            "option2": "Yes but not enough",
            "option3": "Not at all",
            "option4": "A little",
            "answer": "Yes"
        }
    ]
    
}